#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/anas-ahmed-288583158 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Customer Service Teamwork Banking

# **Anas Ahmed**

Implementation Engineer at Euronet Worldwide|Fintech Enthusiast| Visa|MasterCard|Payments & Card Processing| Pakistan

#### Summary

Working with Visa and Matercard to comply banks for various mandates. Vast knowldge of acquiring and issuing of payment cards. Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Customer Service, Banking, C++, Enterprise Architecture, and Teamwork. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Computer Software Engineering from Sir Syed University.

#### Experience

Euronet Worldwide Application Consultant July 2021 - Present (9 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

TPS Worldwide 3 years 7 months

Senior Software Engineer January 2021 - September 2021 (9 months) Pakistan

Software Engineer March 2018 - January 2021 (2 years 11 months) Karachi ,Pakistan

National Bank of Pakistan Intern April 2017 - June 2017 (3 months) I.I Chundrigarh Road, Karachi

Education

## Sir Syed University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Software Engineering · (2014 - 2017)

## SM Public Academy

· (2006 - 2011)